beautynama.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy Policy

**Visitor Notice**  
Beautynama is a Blog and You can Visit it by no Logins or Giving out Your Email Address anywhere except while in Comments  
We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:  
To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  
To help you quickly find services or information on beautynama.  
To help us create content most relevant to you.  
To alert you about updated information and other new services on beautynama.

Visitor Consent  
If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on beautynama, but you will not be able to access areas that require registration like comments area. Beautynama sends regular newsletters, which are sent only to opt-in lists. They also include a very easy and simple way to be removed once you have joined.

Security  
Beautynama strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Third Party Ad Servers  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Beautynama. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message).

Changes to this document  
Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. TechSpot may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.
